We extend a warm welcome to all of our visitors joining us online and in person today. On behalf of our Pastor, First Lady, and the entire congregation — you are welcome here!

# 🎂 August Birthdays

# 🤝 Community Outreach: Memphis Union Mission
The Memphis Union Mission for the Unhoused is in dire need of **cases of bottled water** and **large cans of vegetables**. Please bring donations to the church so we can deliver them to the Mission, or give a monetary donation to **Bro. Fred Armstrong**, who will purchase the needed items on the Mission's behalf.

# 🙏 Prayer List
- Marilyn Smith
- Mother Velma Perkins
- Harold & Carolyn Glover
- Nan Hampton
- Elijah Hunt (Bro. Stanley Echol's nephew), stationed in Jordan, recently bombed
- Helen Jenkins, in the loss of her sister
- Lieutenant Linzie Bogan, who is currently deployed

# Tennessee Fifth Jurisdiction Music Ministry: Youth & Young Adult Choir Rehearsal
Monday, August 17 at 7:00 PM at Faith Heritage COGIC, 3802 Gragg Ave. Youth and young adults are encouraged to participate as we prepare for the August 28 Retirement Concert.

# COGIC International Youth Department: Tennessee State Youth Rally
Saturday, September 19 at 10:00 AM at Holy Temple of Deliverance COGIC, 4020 Mill Branch Rd. Theme: "Thanking God for the Victory." All youth and young adults are encouraged to attend!



